How is it?
It's delicious!
Excuse me!
Coming.
Dai-chan, it's been a while.
Haruko!
Why the sudden visit?
Rin-chan!
Reina-chan?
What's up, Reina-chan?
Are you going out somewhere?
Haruko?
No, we came to visit!
I see!
Um...
Reina-chan, do you like sweet buns?
What are those?
They're round and sweet.
Then I like them!
Well then, Rin, get some barley tea for Reina-chan.
Okay. Let's go, Reina-chan.
We were eating snacks anyway.
I want some too!
Delicious!
I know, right?
I haven't had these before.
Thank you.
It's incredible.
This is the first time I've come here, but it looks like Grandpa's house.
Forget about that. What's up,
bringing along a school bag on a Sunday?
I'm sorry.
To be honest, we ran away from home.
W-Wha-
Won't the people at home be worried?
Why would you do this?
Then, it's that, huh?
What do you mean by "that"?
You know, a problem with your husband.
There's that too.
"Too"?
Yeah!
Then, a problem with his famil-
That too!
Living with your husband's parents must be tough, huh?
I wonder if there's anyone who actually gets along with their in-laws.
Scary!
I don't have any siblings or any other place to go to.
Ah, we use the same textbook for math!
Huh, really?
Is it okay if we stay at your place?
Show me your other textbooks too.
Before that, you need to talk things through
Okay.
Oh, the Japanese textbook is different.
with your parents.
It'll be fine. I left a note at home.
I want to see yours!
I didn't say where we'll be,
Sure, let's go.
but I did write, "I'll make sure to take Reina to school."
I haven't given much thought to anything else.
I haven't told my parents yet.
You haven't thought about it? You have a kid with you, you know.
There was no other way!
I just had to get away from that house,
as soon as possible!
Fine, then.
Let's go buy groceries for dinner.
Dai-chan.
I don't have much, but you can use the room on the right.
It really is different!
Thank you. It's a little heavy.
What the hell did you put in here?
Reina's slippers and textbooks are in there.
Good job on making it this far.
Dai-chan, you usually eat whatever's available, right?
I'll cook you a proper meal.
We don't just eat "whatever."
Daikichi, can we get some sweets?
One each, okay?
Okay!
What kind of meat should we get?
It's all the same.
Not that one.
Here.
This one is a bit...
Daikichi-san! Good afternoon!
Dai-chan! The beef and pork are pretty cheap!
Damn!
Um... This is...
It's not what it looks like!
This is Haruko, a cousin from my mother's side.
What does it matter if I'm from your mother's side?
Oh, I see!
Nice to meet you!
My son is in the same class as Rin-chan, and I'm indebted to Daikichi-san.
Why am I explaining myself when she didn't even ask?
Besides, there's no point in making excuses to her!
My daughter is the same age then.
"It's not what it looks like"?
Really?
I'm Reina.
She just started first grade this year.
I'm Kouki.
Yo, Kouki.
What kind of sweets did you pick?
Sup, Daikichi.
This one.
Deluxe Big Nyan Gum!
Vegetable Castella for me!
I'm getting the Nyan Nyan Kitty Candy!
Are those really sweets?
She was beautiful, wasn't she?
W-Well, I guess she's pretty good looking for a mom.
Don't try to have an affair with her or anything, though.
A-Are you an idiot?!
It's not like that at all!
Besides, she has her hands full
living alone with Kouki,
so she doesn't have time!
Just them two?
Moron! You've been watching too many weird dramas!
I guess she's like two or three years older than us.
H-How should I know?
So she's divorced, right?
Not sure.
This looks tasty!
This is the first time I've had this!
I tried some new things.
When we're at home, I have to prioritize my mother-in-law's preferences.
Mama, I want this at home too!
Well then, time to eat!
Time to eat!
It's delicious!
Thank you, Rin-chan.
Reina, hold your chopsticks properly.
Okay!
The floor creaks!
Reina, take this towel.
Okay!
What's that?
It's a bra!
Reina! Don't pull it!
Are they asleep?
Yeah, finally.
Looks like they both got too excited.
I moved Rin-chan to your futon, Dai-chan.
Thank you.
Thanks.
That hits the spot!
Been a while since I've had alcohol.
Want something to eat?
I gain weight easily these days, so I'll pass.
I guess so.
Do I look like I've gained weight?
Not at all. I'm just saying, we're finally in our 30's.
I wish I could go back to just being 30.
We're different from when we were young,
so we need to be careful.
Even if I say that, my husband doesn't care anymore.
I don't know why I'm working so hard.
Haruko.
What?
When you guys were in the bath earlier, I called your in-laws.
Why?! Dai-chan, don't do anything weird!
It's not weird. They would worry, wouldn't they?
I just told them that you two are okay
and that you'd be staying here for a while.
I didn't tell them my address or anything.
I left a letter for them, so just let it go!
That's not the point. It may be fine for you but not for Reina.
Reina's with me, and she's doing fine, so it's all right.
That's true, but if the people waiting don't know where she is or if she's okay,
I don't think they'll see things the same way.
I don't care about them.
Calm down a little, Haruko.
Rin-chan.
Do you want to trouble them?
Come inside.
That's my nose!
Papa and Mama are always fighting.
Even though they're married?
Yeah, even so.
I always pretend to sleep when that happens.
Let's hold hands.
That tickles.
That's my cheek.
Every single day...
Ever since I got married, I've been keeping my feelings bottled up!
What's wrong with causing them a little trouble?
I'm sorry, Dai-chan.
I said something strange.
No problem.
I'm going to sleep.
Dai-chan.
Good night.
Rin-chan?
Good morning!
Good morning. Rin-chan, you're making breakfast?
Yeah. Good morning to you too, Daikichi!
You're up early today.
Well, yeah.
Dai-chan, you make Rin-chan cook for you?
D-Don't be stupid! We always cook together!
When we need to use the stove, I-
No fighting!
You're getting rice on your face.
Finish eating soon, okay?
We need to take the train to school today.
Rin-chan!
What is that, this early in the morning?
It's Kouki-kun.
Yeah, yeah! Just come in already!
You're annoying the neighbors!
Rin-chan, is your school far away?
You leave this early?
No.
Kouki-kun's mom is really busy, so he comes over pretty early.
G-Good morning.
Daikichi, did you get married?!
No, I didn't! She's my cousin!
Oh. You're not married after all.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Daikichi, do you want to get married?
Well, that's-
Mama, you'd prefer being single, right?
What does "being single" mean?
It means not being married.
I know that! Being divorced, right?
I don't know what "divorced" means.
Your mom is married but would prefer to be single,
and Daikichi is single but would prefer to be married?
Adults are weird.
They sure are.
Daikichi, can I have a rice ball?
You had breakfast before coming over, right?
Yeah, I did.
Fine, go ahead.
It was supposed to be mine, though.
All right!
Didn't you have breakfast before coming over?
Why are you eating again?
You're way too nice, Dai-chan.
Is that a problem? What's your point?
Why, just because I gave him a rice ball?
I'm not talking about that.
You're busy too, aren't you?
I guess you really do care about that pretty mom.
I-Idiot! That again?
I just want to help her out.
Rin seems to get along with them too,
but that's all there is to it.
I don't know the details,
but I'm sure they've been through a lot.
It'd be rude if I'm too forward.
I guess it's hard for a woman to live alone, huh?
Reina, didn't I say you're going to be late if you don't hurry?
Haruko...
Good morning!
Good morning.
Don't tell anyone about staying over.
Why?
Just keep it a secret, okay?
Okay!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Reina-chan, you came with your mother?
Yeah, I did.
We secretly ran away from home, so I had to come by train today.
What's with that?
Hey, wait up!
I told you hold onto it, didn't I?
I'm not going to get you another one.
Maybe it'll get home before we do.
Yeah, maybe it will.
Good work!
Oh, you're working late today?
Yeah, my husband is taking care of the kid.
Is Yuu-kun doing well?
He sure is.
He's been so energetic lately, I don't know what to do with him.
It's good that your husband helps you out with that.
This is the first time!
His business trip got canceled, so he has a day off.
Besides, I can't let my husband do all the parenting.
Hurry up! Reina-chan's waiting!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm home! Reina-chan!
They went to sleep pretty early today.
Haruko, you don't intend to make a big deal out of this, do you?
Are you talking about getting a divorce?
Yeah, that.
No, that's not going to happen.
I was worried for nothing, then.
I've thought about it several times, though.
Actually, I've been thinking about it every day.
I mean, once you start thinking of your husband as your enemy, that's it.
Other than Reina, everyone else is either an enemy or a stranger.
It's like the two of us make up the whole family to me,
but I guess that's not realistic.
Thinking about Reina, how much I make,
and how many hurdles I had to overcome before getting to that point...
I guess it's better for me to stay as I am now.
I got married right after getting a job.
When I was younger, all I thought about was being a good wife.
There's no other way, right?
It's the only way to keep Reina safe.
I never really thought about getting married,
but I guess having a normal family is hard too.
Well, you do it all by yourself.
That's pretty amazing.
No. I'm not doing anything at all.
That's not true. Rin-chan looks like she's having fun.
She cooks your meals for you and everything!
They're working hard over at Kouki-kun's place too, right?
And I can work hard with Reina.
All this talk about two people...
Did you talk about this with your husband?
He keeps working overtime,
so I don't get to talk to him often.
So I'll just have to work hard with Reina.
I've already managed to deal with it for so many years.
I'm sure I can keep doing so in the future.
If I just shut my feelings away, then I can get through most of the stuff.
That sounds really unhealthy.
It's the opposite. If I didn't do it, I'd snap.
You've gotten a lot stronger, Haruko.
Have I?
Once you start raising a kid, there are times you need to be really strong,
especially when they're babies.
I don't know much about when they're babies.
When you keep at it, you naturally get used to it.
I really don't want to grow old.
I never wanted to be strong in the first place.
I just wanted to stay a girl forever.
Sorry, Dai-chan, and thank you.
I'll go back home tomorrow.
I see.
What does it mean to be married?
What does it mean to be a parent?
What's wrong? It's your turn, Reina.
What's wrong?
I knew it!
Knew what?
It's Papa's car!
Papa is coming after work.
He wouldn't come so early.
It's definitely Papa. I can't be wrong!
You are wrong! Reina!
Papa!
I was worried about you, Reina.
I was worried too!
Sorry about that.
So he can get off work around this time if he wants to, huh?
Don't say it like that!
Working for a company can be pretty rough, you know?
Hideyuki-san, you idiot.
I'm very sorry.
Haruko caused you a lot of trouble.
Not at all! I didn't really-
I sincerely apologize.
Damn, I'm not dressed appropriately at all!
Thank you so much, Dai-chan.
Papa didn't even think to carry our luggage.
He's so inconsiderate.
He really is!
Come over again sometime.
I don't want to cause you any more trouble than I already have.
That's not it.
Rin would like to see Reina-chan again.
Thank you, Dai-chan.
Mama, Mama! Can we come back this Sunday?
We can't do that, Reina.
The Haruko that was always crying as a kid
and the Haruko that said she wanted to stay a little girl forever yesterday...
Bye, then.
Don't pack so much stuff next time.
It's hard to watch.
Not a chance.
A woman always carries a lot.
This is nothing.
Bye bye!
I'll see you off!
How's this?
Nice.
But this might suit you more.
What do you think?
Can I try this one on too?
Sure, go ahead.
I'm thirsty!
We just need to try on some clothes.
How about this one?
Um, I'll just go look at some stuff with Kouki.
Sure.
See, it looks great on you!
You're so cute, Rin-chan!
You like it?
It tastes like summer!
Yeah!